Hello friends, farmer brothers, you are welcome,
you all must be knowing that I am
not making videos on anything else, Mandi Bhaav and I have my own
channel, you all know that I am
not making videos on anything else, what was the current price of pulses
and on Monday I gave my paper for
ICC Prudential
Insurance, what is this, it is a
branch of ICC Bank, I got selected in it, I
gave the paper through the paper, I will
qualify it and now what do I do nowadays,
what is life insurance, I do health
insurance, life insurance and what is there, if
farmer brothers help me a little in this, it will be even
better because I have
made that video also and what is the
target in this, I get Rs
5 lakh, Rs 10 lakh for monthly life insurance, so I
want to tell all the farmer brothers accordingly that my target has been achieved, I will keep
making videos to you, what is going on
in Mandi Bhaav, that will also be achieved and yours will
also be reduced, and if some people are interested
then you can do it tomorrow, I will give my number on the screen
and this is my card, you can see it
[Music]
So all the farmer brothers are requested to
please support and I will also reach further, right now
I am in our branch  I have a
branch in Guna, I am a
Madari with the license of this provincial, right now I have to come to the branch daily, due to this
I am
not making videos and I also have to work on the field,
I have to
meet a lot of farmer brothers, farmer
brothers and these government people because
what is there in life insurance, life insurance is a guarantee,
what is the identity in it, if an accident happens then it gets
updated, he gets money and
through this if you keep depositing little by little then you get it
together,
after 10-12 years then this is less in it and I
request all the farmer brothers to
support me as much as possible and I will
also make videos for you, please if you achieve
my target then it is good and if
anyone is interested then what will come out of my target, it
is available for Rs 25000, if I
tell the truth then what is the commission, you keep the commission,
I have to perform, I should reach the
best and best people in this bank,
this is the reason and what is the commission,
whoever is interested in
completing my target then he will get it  I will give you
commission for this, you
can call me tomorrow on this confirmed number on your phone
related to this, till then
Ram Ram to all the farmer brothers and we will meet
in the next video and what am I doing now, I will
start that video from tomorrow also, all the farmer
brothers, what is the going on price of grains in Pashu Nagar Mandi
and if any mistake has happened then I
apologize to all the farmer brothers
because since 15th, I am not making videos
of pulses for 15 days, if you listen to the voice
of the Mandi then till then Ram Ram to all the farmer brothers,
with this in the next video